<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title></title>
 <link href="http://www.vigneshr.in//atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://www.vigneshr.in//"/>
 <updated>2017-06-19T20:30:42+05:30</updated>
 <id>http://www.vigneshr.in</id>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Don't Forget!</title>
   <link href="http://www.vigneshr.in//dont-forget/"/>
   <updated>2015-10-16T01:35:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>http://www.vigneshr.in/dont-forget</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I am sure there are times, you would have forgotten things and I did too. When I was checking online for a solution on this people where area asking us to write notes about what to be done and use it to remind ourself. An important step is you have to write it and keep it in a place which you remember and you also need to remember taking this note and going through the list which is as equal as remembering things. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I wanted to solve it in easy way. So, I started connecting things in my activity which makes me to remember only one key factor in the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, You are asked to bring documents to the office, the main activity in this process will be your journey from home to the office which you will do eventually. So, tag your documents to your car/bike keys. So next day it will be easy for you to take the documents to the office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is that simple. Find important thing in your activity and connect things which you want to remember. Happy Remembering!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Television Advertisements about Television!</title>
   <link href="http://www.vigneshr.in//television-advertisement/"/>
   <updated>2015-10-03T03:40:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>http://www.vigneshr.in/television-advertisement</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have seen many large electronics corporations do showcase their television product in the Ads. Sometimes they talk about quality of the picture contrast ration pixel density. Funny part is most of the people watch in different television which is almost will no way be compared to the TV shown in the Ads. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;720&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/8dq8cUA8pDI&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;720&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Zfbh6vGR3kA&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like above videos many used to split the screens in the advertisement and showcase that their product is better. My question is does it generate any value to the customer. For example when some organisation displayed some ads to showcase their picture quality is really good, I was watching it through my television which displayed the pretty perfectly then why should I change it? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: I am not here blame any Ad agencies or any corporate. I am just presenting my thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>WhatsApp Everywhere!</title>
   <link href="http://www.vigneshr.in//whatsapp-everywhere/"/>
   <updated>2015-10-02T04:30:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>http://www.vigneshr.in/whatsapp-everywhere</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It is a long weekend, So I planned a travel to Chennai to visit my friends. As usual booked a ticket in RedBus to travel and got into pickup bus. To my surprise, the bus was full and I was asked to stand with assurance from the driver that it will not take more than 15 min. There was a guy who was sitting, looked at me and smiled, I didn&amp;#39;t know the reason at that time but when it took an hour to reach Majestic(Bangalore Bus Terminus), I just smiled back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was standing in the bus, I took my phone and informed my sister that I boarded the bus. After pinging her, I just glanced away from the phone to find a surprise that everyone in the bus where using WhatsApp. No, I haven&amp;#39;t read at other people conversation. I was thinking, Mark you made a good purchase. Then I was analysing what caused people to use WhatsApp to be precise what caused people to turn WhatsApping as their behaviour to talk to friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From my perspective following are the points that make me believe things that make WhatsApp a big success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even though they say that they are freemium and people have to pay $1 after a year of use, I don&amp;#39;t remember that I ever paid them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They really concentrated on the developing markets like India, Brazil and made their app work on even the weakest network and cheap phone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Network effect: People brought in other people to the app because they found value in it and wanted to share the same with their friends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bundling with carriers to provide free data for using WhatsApp, I think this is the groundbreaking move&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I get additional thoughts, will update. If you also do have some thoughts, please comment below lets have a discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being overall said, I really like WhatsApp team because they taught me how to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;stay lean and move faster&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How Mom teach her child!</title>
   <link href="http://www.vigneshr.in//mom-inspiration/"/>
   <updated>2015-09-30T06:39:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>http://www.vigneshr.in/mom-inspiration</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;fb-video&quot; 
    data-href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/OMGParadisePage/videos/882441295112294/&quot; 
    data-width=&quot;800&quot; 
    data-autoplay=&quot;true&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I came across this video in my facebook feed, which is like amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I always do wonder how come so many businessman without an MBA or any business degrees were able to run a successful business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I think, I got part of an answer, these people get it correct by doing things and getting failed or by looking at others failure in their business.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Hello, World!</title>
   <link href="http://www.vigneshr.in//hello-world/"/>
   <updated>2015-09-29T16:10:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>http://www.vigneshr.in/hello-world</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone, thanks for visiting my blog. I will be writing about my learnings and findings from web. Hope I learn things on this process and share things which are useful for both of us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you find some of my writing were wrong, please feel free to comment and teach me.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
