<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Vignesh Rajendran</title>
    <description>Web Enthusiast</description>
    <link>http://www.vigneshr.in</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.vigneshr.in/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Don't Forget!</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;I am sure there are times, you would have forgotten things and I did too. When I was checking online for a solution on this people where area asking us to write notes about what to be done and use it to remind ourself. An important step is you have to write it and keep it in a place which you remember and you also need to remember taking this note and going through the list which is as equal as remembering things. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 01:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.vigneshr.in/dont-forget/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.vigneshr.in/dont-forget/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Television Advertisements about Television!</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;I have seen many large electronics corporations do showcase their television product in the Ads. Sometimes they talk about quality of the picture contrast ration pixel density. Funny part is most of the people watch in different television which is almost will no way be compared to the TV shown in the Ads. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2015 03:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.vigneshr.in/television-advertisement/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.vigneshr.in/television-advertisement/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WhatsApp Everywhere!</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;It is a long weekend, So I planned a travel to Chennai to visit my friends. As usual booked a ticket in RedBus to travel and got into pickup bus. To my surprise, the bus was full and I was asked to stand with assurance from the driver that it will not take more than 15 min. There was a guy who was sitting, looked at me and smiled, I didn&amp;#39;t know the reason at that time but when it took an hour to reach Majestic(Bangalore Bus Terminus), I just smiled back.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 04:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.vigneshr.in/whatsapp-everywhere/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.vigneshr.in/whatsapp-everywhere/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Mom teach her child!</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;div class=&quot;fb-video&quot; 
    data-href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/OMGParadisePage/videos/882441295112294/&quot; 
    data-width=&quot;800&quot; 
    data-autoplay=&quot;true&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 06:39:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.vigneshr.in/mom-inspiration/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.vigneshr.in/mom-inspiration/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello, World!</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone, thanks for visiting my blog. I will be writing about my learnings and findings from web. Hope I learn things on this process and share things which are useful for both of us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 16:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.vigneshr.in/hello-world/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.vigneshr.in/hello-world/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>